[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "You excited?", "question_tokens": ["You", "excited", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "When can we expect any kind of funeral?", "question_tokens": ["When", "can", "we", "expect", "any", "kind", "of", "funeral", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "What is your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Well, my view is that it seems that the authorities have done everything they could.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "view", "is", "that", "it", "seems", "that", "the", "authorities", "have", "done", "everything", "they", "could", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Russia"]}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "But in terms of the bomb making, do you really think with your old hat on that this is likely that they just learned how to do this off the Internet and the first time they try it, it works perfectly twice?", "question_tokens": ["But", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "bomb", "making", ",", "do", "you", "really", "think", "with", "your", "old", "hat", "on", "that", "this", "is", "likely", "that", "they", "just", "learned", "how", "to", "do", "this", "off", "the", "Internet", "and", "the", "first", "time", "they", "try", "it", ",", "it", "works", "perfectly", "twice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Well, it's conceivable to me that they even learned some of these techniques over a period of time, including when they were in Russia, but again, I go back to the question about whether this plot was directed by somebody else, or whether this was kind of a lone wolf, self-radicalized and basically self-motivated kind of event as opposed to externally directed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "conceivable", "to", "me", "that", "they", "even", "learned", "some", "of", "these", "techniques", "over", "a", "period", "of", "time", ",", "including", "when", "they", "were", "in", "Russia", ",", "but", "again", ",", "I", "go", "back", "to", "the", "question", "about", "whether", "this", "plot", "was", "directed", "by", "somebody", "else", ",", "or", "whether", "this", "was", "kind", "of", "a", "lone", "wolf", ",", "self-radicalized", "and", "basically", "self-motivated", "kind", "of", "event", "as", "opposed", "to", "externally", "directed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Shouldn't alarm bells at least have gone off given we now know the Russian authorities had contacted the FBI and the CIA about this guy?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "n't", "alarm", "bells", "at", "least", "have", "gone", "off", "given", "we", "now", "know", "the", "Russian", "authorities", "had", "contacted", "the", "FBI", "and", "the", "CIA", "about", "this", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "JJS", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Well, it's not as if we didn't do anything.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "as", "if", "we", "did", "n't", "do", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI", "CIA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Can I ask you both if that is a correct assessment of your positions?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "ask", "you", "both", "if", "that", "is", "a", "correct", "assessment", "of", "your", "positions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "It's not.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Why do you think he should be executed for that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "he", "should", "be", "executed", "for", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "He should be executed because the death penalty is the only punishment that fits the crime.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "should", "be", "executed", "because", "the", "death", "penalty", "is", "the", "only", "punishment", "that", "fits", "the", "crime", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "What's your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Well, first of all, I'm opposed to torture under all circumstances.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "'m", "opposed", "to", "torture", "under", "all", "circumstances", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "How courageous is it to have put that woman through eight years of I guess what turned out to be a lie?", "question_tokens": ["How", "courageous", "is", "it", "to", "have", "put", "that", "woman", "through", "eight", "years", "of", "I", "guess", "what", "turned", "out", "to", "be", "a", "lie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "Look, she's made it clear that she's proud of him.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "she", "'s", "made", "it", "clear", "that", "she", "'s", "proud", "of", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Does it tarnish at all, do you think, what he has done?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "tarnish", "at", "all", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "what", "he", "has", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "I suppose my obvious question to you is, how do you feel about all the events of the past week?", "question_tokens": ["I", "suppose", "my", "obvious", "question", "to", "you", "is", ",", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "all", "the", "events", "of", "the", "past", "week", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "You know, for me, it's a lot of mixed emotions.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "for", "me", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "mixed", "emotions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["past weekend", "Monday"]}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "When he called you last week, what did he say to you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "he", "called", "you", "last", "week", ",", "what", "did", "he", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "He actually called this past weekend and we spoke a couple of times on Monday.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "actually", "called", "this", "past", "weekend", "and", "we", "spoke", "a", "couple", "of", "times", "on", "Monday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "CC", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Did he apologize to you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "apologize", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "I think he's in the process of taking ownership of the here and now, which is actually coming out, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "in", "the", "process", "of", "taking", "ownership", "of", "the", "here", "and", "now", ",", "which", "is", "actually", "coming", "out", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "And what do you think of a debate now that the one who survived should get the death penalty?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "a", "debate", "now", "that", "the", "one", "who", "survived", "should", "get", "the", "death", "penalty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "WP", "VBN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Well, I don't think that this issue has much to do with immigrants versus Americans.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "this", "issue", "has", "much", "to", "do", "with", "immigrants", "versus", "Americans", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Would you execute Dzhokhar Tsarnaev if he's convicted?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "execute", "Dzhokhar", "Tsarnaev", "if", "he", "'s", "convicted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "I don't know the whole story.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "the", "whole", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dzhokhar Tsarnaev"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "What do you say to the cynics who say you just can't have any kind of comprehensive immigration package of this type that works?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "the", "cynics", "who", "say", "you", "just", "ca", "n't", "have", "any", "kind", "of", "comprehensive", "immigration", "package", "of", "this", "type", "that", "works", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Well, I think that it's a very complicated issue.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "a", "very", "complicated", "issue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "In simple terms, what do you think is the best, quickest, most effective way to get this immigration issue under control?", "question_tokens": ["In", "simple", "terms", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "is", "the", "best", ",", "quickest", ",", "most", "effective", "way", "to", "get", "this", "immigration", "issue", "under", "control", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", ",", "JJS", ",", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Well, there is really no easy way and simple way.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "is", "really", "no", "easy", "way", "and", "simple", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "What are the things you found most effective?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "things", "you", "found", "most", "effective", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "JJS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "I think that one of the things that I think I believe in is that you have to secure the border.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "one", "of", "the", "things", "that", "I", "think", "I", "believe", "in", "is", "that", "you", "have", "to", "secure", "the", "border", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130430pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "And drones, as John McCain says?", "question_tokens": ["And", "drones", ",", "as", "John", "McCain", "says", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "You know, drones or no drones, in other words, you need the man power there.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "drones", "or", "no", "drones", ",", "in", "other", "words", ",", "you", "need", "the", "man", "power", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John McCain"]}}]